azazie.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Azazie

#### PRIVACY STATEMENT

Your privacy is very important to us. We collect important customer information to personalize and enhance your shopping experience. This information lets us communicate with our customers about our products, services, and promotions.

Accordingly, we have developed this  Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. By visiting and using the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### YOUR INFORMATION

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address, phone, and email address.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing: We may send you emails about our store, new products, and other updates.

#### CONSENT

**How do you get my consent?**  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [customerservice@azazie.com](mailto:customerservice@azazie.com)

#### DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

#### THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use, and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

We use third-party payment service providers, such as payment gateways, fraud detection, and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. We don’t store credit card or payment information.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

#### SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

We store all passwords in encrypted format. Order information including name, order, address, phone, and email address are stored securely on our servers.

#### COOKIES

As you browse our site, your preferences are remembered through temporary use of cookies. Cookies enable our system to monitor the navigational preferences. We May also use technologies to provide your with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests.

#### AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

#### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please email [customerservice@azazie.com](mailto:customerservice@azazie.com)
